# Akash Pawara



linkedin.com/in/akashpawara



akashpawara29@gmail.com



https://akashpawara-portfolio.netlify.app



7506021898

## Summary

I'm a Full Stack Web Developer with enthusiasm and focus on Front-End Development. I have a strong commitment towards self learning and willing to learn new skills as needed. I have 3 years of experience with PHP, MySQL, Front-end Development, JQuery and ES/ES6+ JavaScript. I have recently started learning & building applications in MERN stack.

## **Experience**



## Web Developer

University of Mumbai

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020 (4 months)

Developed a full stack web platform for Health center of University of Mumbai which digitizes the workflow of a health clinic. It consist of Doctor's as well as Receptionist's panel which constructs the flow of a patient's admit & discharge process, preserving medical history & prescriptions, generating reports based on gender, Diabetes & Hepatitis B.

### Edilui Python Developer

Eduvance

Jun 2018 - Jul 2018 (2 months)

Developed python scripts for tracking Inventory, storing or retrieving data from excel sheets. Developed a web scrapper using python. Developed a phone book software in python. Developed a smtp session to verify users.

#### **Education**



# ■ Vidyalankar Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering 2017 - 2020



# Vivekanand education society of polytechnic

Diploma, Computer Engineering Technology/Technician 2015 - 2017

### **Licenses & Certifications**



AI For Everyone - deeplearning.ai



Version Control with Git - Atlassian

### **Honors & Awards**



### Smart India Hackathon 2019 Winner (Software Edition) - SIH

Mar 2019

Developed Solution for real-time car accident reports generation with insurance dispute. Location: IIT-BHU (Varanasi)

#### **Skills**